Guide to the First Baptist Church of Ithaca records, 1811-2005.
First Baptist Church of Ithaca records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
First Baptist Church of Ithaca records, 1811-2005.
2004
First Baptist Church of Ithaca.
21.6 cubic ft., 2 tape recordings
Correspondence, scrapbooks, pamphlets, books, minutes, tape recordings, architectural plans.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Materials from the Board of Trustees, boards of deacons and deaconesses, and church meetings; lists of members, baptisms, and funerals; records of women's and youth organizations; Sunday School materials; letters from donors to the church building fund. Tape recordings of services; plans for remodelling the church; records of the Danby Baptist Church and the First Baptist Church of Christ of Ithaca.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of the Board of Trustees, boards of deacons and deaconesses, and church meetings; lists of members, baptisms, and funerals; minutes statistics and correspondence of various church officials and boards; constitution; financial records; minutes, reports, accounts, and other records of various women's and youth organizations, including the Women's Missionary Society, Women's Union, and Women's Fellowship; Sunday School rolls and minutes; various other letters, resolutions, pamphlets, scrapbooks, photographs, hymn books, church newsletters, historical data, and letters from donors to the church building fund, 1889-91. There are also tape recordings of services conducted by Rev. Christian B. Jensen; plans for remodelling the church, Clarence A. Martin, architect, 1930-32; and records of the Danby Baptist Church and the First Baptist Church of Christ of Ithaca, 1811-38.
SUBJECTS
Names:
First Baptist Church of Ithaca.; Jensen, Christian B.; Martin, Clarence A.; Danby Baptist Church.; First Baptist Church of Christ of Ithaca.
Subjects:
Baptists.; Church architecture.; Missionaries.; Religion.; Women in church work.; Women in missionary work.
Form and Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Hymnals.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 8 (pledging/gift records) restricted until 18 July 2047; Box 10 (Pulpit Committee) restricted until 18 July 2067
SERIES LIST
Series I. General files
Series II. Letters regarding construction of new church
Series III. Church history
Series IV. Renovation, 1970s
Series V. Cash Books
Series VI. Media
Series VII. Studies and drawings for remodelling of the First Baptist Church, Ithaca, N.Y., 1930-1932
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. General files
  - Vol. of minutes, index in back of vol., 1821-1838 (Box 1)
    Dolly Cornell Letter, Apr. 13, 1834 No Coon or Snow Entries.
  - Vol. of minutes, index in back of vol., 1838-1866 (Box 1)
    No Cornell or Coon entries.
  - Vol. of minutes., 1866-1895 (Box 1)
    No Cornell or Coon entries, but Mrs. Cora A. Snow entry (bapt. June 4, 1893)
  - Trustees' vol., no index., 1827-1905 (Box 2)
    Loose leg. fld. with material removed from volumes in orig. acc., alphabetical list of members, n.d., no Coon or Cornell entries, but a Mary J. Snow, dismissed Sept. 2, 1857, dismissed Feb. 18, 1858.
  - Record Book, 1895-1915 (Box 2)
  - Record Book, 1916-1932 (Box 2)
  - Record Book, 1932-1940 (Box 3)
  - Record Book, 1940-1947 (Box 3)
  - Record Book, 1947-1948 (Box 3)
  - Record Book, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1950-1951 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1951-1952 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1952-1953 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1953-1954 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
  - Record Book, 1955-1956 (Box 5)
  - Record Book, 1956-1957 (Box 5)
  - Record Book, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Record Book, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
  - Record Book, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Early Records, 1827, 1833, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1914-1936 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1926-1934 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Records, 1928-1934 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1929-1937 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees Records, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1934-1937 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1934-1945 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Official Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees Records, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1942-1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Secretary, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1945-1952 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, etc., 1947-1953 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Building Alterations, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees Mortgages, 1952-1957 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1953-1956 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Contracts, Correspondence, Misc., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees Records, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1958-1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1958-1970 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, etc., 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, etc., 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Deaconesses, 1937-1953 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Deaconesses, 1954-1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Deaconesses, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Deacons, 1929-1950 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Deacons, 1929-1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Deacons Minutes, 1963-1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Diaconate, 1959-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Diaconate, 1961-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Austin Organ Co., 1931-1932 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Unified Fund - Building Project, 1952-1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Historic Structure Project, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Building, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fund Raising - Building, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Building, 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Building - Joyce Finch's File, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Building - Friends of 1st Baptist, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Copy of Historic Structure Report from Egner, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Every Member Canvas, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Pledges and Contributions, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Pledges and Contributions, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Pledges and Contributions, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Ledger, 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Ledger, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Ledger, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Ledger, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Ledger, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Trust Funds, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Financial Records, 1959 (Box 8)
  - Financial Records, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Financial Records, 1961 (Box 8)
  - Financial Records, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Financial Records, 1963 (Box 8)
  - Financial Records, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Financial Records, 1915-1918, 1924-1925 (Box 9)
  - Financial Records, 1930-1955 (Box 9)
  - Pulpit Committee - Minutes, ministerial service records, correspondence re pastor candidates, 1949-1966 (Box 10)
  - Seneca Baptist Association, 1910-1924 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Seneca Baptist Association, 1927-1959 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Seneca Baptist Association, 1952-1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Seneca Baptist Association, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - History of the Seneca Baptist Association, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1945-1960 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1958-1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1963-1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Board of Christian Education, 196?-1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Board of Missions - Minutes, 1958-1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Christian Higher Education Challenge, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Church School - Roll Book, 1913-1916 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Church School - Roll Book, 1941-1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Church School, 1945-1949 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Church School - Roll Book, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Church School, 1949-1954 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Church School Secretary's Record Book, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Church School, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Church School Secretary's Record Book, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Church School Secretary's Record Book, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Farther Lights Society, 1916-1923 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Farther Lights Society, 1923-1925 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Friendship Group, 1948-1966 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Home Department, 1916-1922 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Northrup Circle, 1881 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Northrup Circle, 1905-1940 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Northrup Circle Minutes, 1924-1939 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Northrup Circle Treasurer, 1926-1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Northrup Circle Miscellaneous Records (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Northrup Circle Class records, misc. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Northrup Circle Receipts, bank books (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Miss Jennie Northrup portraits (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Philathea Class, 1912-1920 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Philathea Class, 1916, 1948-1952 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Philathea Class, 1922-1937 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Philathea Class, 1923-1936 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Philathea Class, 1927-1934 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Philathea Class, 1935-1941 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Philathea Class, 1941-1945 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Philathea Class, 1945-1949 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Philathea Class, 1949-1957 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Philathea Class, 1953-1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Baraca - Philathea News, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Teen Age Guild, 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Town and Gown, 1938-1959 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Ladies Union, 1902-1907 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Ladies Union Executive Committee, 1902-1907 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Treasurer's Book, 1902-1914 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - The Womans Mission Circle, Book A, 1902-1917 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Ladies Union Executive Committee, 1907-1912 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Ladies Union Executive Committee, 1908-1916 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Womans Union, 1916-1923 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Red Cross/White Cross, 1917-1927 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Womans Union, 1921-1926 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Womans Union - Executive Board, 1926-1929 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Womans Union Quarterly Meetings, Book I, 1926-1930 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Womans Union Minutes, Book II, 1930-1939 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Women's Missionary Society/White Cross, 1931-1954 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Women's Union Role Call and Minute Book, 1935-1946 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Women's Union, 1935-1937 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Women's Missionary Society Treasurer, 1938-1946 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Women's Union, 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Women's Missionary Society Secretary's Book, 1939-1943 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Women's Union, 1942-1950 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Women's Fellowship, Missionary Society, 1942-1956 (Box 13, Folder x)
  - Missionary Society Minutes, 1943-1950 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Missionary Society Treasurer's Book, 1944-1950 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Missionary Society Secretary's Book, c. 1945 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Women's Union - Chapter Records, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Women's Fellowship Bazaar Records, 1947-1954 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Women's Union, Treasurer, 1947-1955 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Women's Fellowship - Women's Union, 1949-1955 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Women's Society - Annual Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Women's Fellowship, 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Women's Society - Annual Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Women's Fellowship, 1955-1958 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Circle 3, 1955-1959 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Women's Society - Records and Annual Reports, 1958-1961 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Women's Fellowship - "60 Years of Women's Work", 1960 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - World Wide Guild (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor, 1892, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor, 1896-1921 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Missionary Work - Africa (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - American Indians (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - American Negroes (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Burma (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - China (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - China (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Missionary Work China (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - France (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - India (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Japan (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Mexico, Central and South America, West Indies (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Missionary Work Mormonism (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - North America (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Phillipines (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Missionary Training (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Missionary Training (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Missionary Training (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Missionary Training (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Church History, 1926, 1933, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Dedication of Window in Memory of Mrs. Jane Fleming (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Church and Congregation Membership, 1893 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Membership Lists, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Membership Lists, 1966-1967, 1971, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Manuals (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - The Waymark Vol. No. 1 to Vol. 3 No. 2, 1878-1882 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - The Park Baptist, 1888-1894 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - The First Baptist, 1894-1900 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - The First Baptist, 1895 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1961-1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1972, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Addresses, Special Services, Bulletins, 1886-1972, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Miscellany (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Bulletins, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bulletins, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bulletins, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bulletins, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bulletins, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bulletins, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Bulletins, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Bulletins, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Bulletins, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bulletins, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bulletins, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Vol. The Baptist Encyclopedia, 1881 (Box 15)
  - Vols. Christian Worship and Praise (2 copies), 1939 (Box 15)
  - The News Sheet/The Visitor, 1956-1970 (Box 16)
  - Photographs (Box 17)
  - Photograph, Photograph Albums (2), Citation, Broadside, Recording, Newsclippings, Scrapbooks 1958-1964, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
  - Certificate of Membership issued by the World Wide Baraca Philathea Union to the Men's Baraca Bible Class of 1904 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Newsletters and other publications (Box 19)
  - Long-range Planning Records, 1971 (Box 20)
  - Building Renovation Records, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Sunday Bulletins, 1976-1983 (Box 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1960-1986 (Box 20)
  - Sermons by David M. Evans, 1974-1987 (Box 20)
  - Commission on Human Rights Records (Box 20)
  - The Visitor, Feb.-Apr. 1965 (Box 21)
  - The Visitor, Oct.-Dec. 1966 (Box 21)
  - The Visitor, June 1967 (Box 21)
  - The Visitor, 1977-1984 (Box 21)
  - Church Ads, 1975-1984 (Box 22)
  - Board of Trustees, 1960-1984 (Box 22)
  - Guest Register, 1951-1959 (Box 22)
  - Book: The Pastor in a Teaching Church (Evans) (Box 22)
  - Copper printing plates: Sanctuary of First Baptist (Box 22)
  - White Cross Work (Box 22)
  - Personnel, 1973-1975 (Box 22)
  - Chemung-Steuben Association, 1960-1983 (Box 22)
  - Church activities to 1985 (Box 22)
  - Annual Reports to American Baptist Convention, 1941-1951 (Box 23)
  - Annual Reports to American Baptist Convention, 1960-1984 (Box 23)
  - Annual Reports to American Baptist Convention, 1960-1967 (Box 23)
  - Church and Church School Attendance (Box 23)
  - Church Clerk, 1966-1984 (Box 24)
  - Membership and Friends Annual Listing, 1978-1984 (Box 24)
  - New Members and Death, 1974-1982 (Box 24)
  - Transfers, 1967-1973, 1952-1962 (Box 24)
  - Sunday Bulletins, 973-1984 (Box 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1941-1943, 1950-1952, 1972-1984 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1984 (Box 24)
  - Building Use Contracts (Box 25)
  - Board of Missions, 1965-1970 (Box 25)
  - Seneca Baptist Association Reports, 1959, 1960, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Ithaca College Ministry, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Action (Box 25)
  - Cuba (Box 25)
  - Alive in Mission (Box 25)
  - Women's Fellowship, 1955-1969 (Box 25)
  - News Clippings (friends, members, church activities), 1973-1983 (Box 25)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 25)
  - Bulletin, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Visitor, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Canvass, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - News clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Board of Christian Education, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Trustees, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Worship and Christian Concern, 1985-1989 (Box 27)
  - Retreats, Before 1990 (Box 27)
  - Committee - Parable of Talents, 1980s (Box 27)
  - Church Cabinet, 1980s (Box 27)
  - Church Clerk, 1989 (Box 27)
  - Annual Report, American Baptist Convention, 1985-1990 (Box 27)
  - Financial Records, 1971, 1975, 1978, 1980, 1984-1990 (Box 28)
  - Seneca Baptist Association Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 28)
  - Sixty Years of Women's Work, 1960 (Box 28)
  - Hopes and Dreams, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Music Committee, 1974-1989 (Box 28)
  - Tompkins County Religious Workers Association, 1980s (Box 28)
  - ABC Statements of Concern, 1985 (Box 28)
  - Constitution, 1952, 1964, 1995 (Box 28)
  - Sunday School Records, 1970s- (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous File (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1990-2005 (Box 30)
  - Newspaper ads/articles, 1990-2005 (Box 30)
  - Church Cookbook, Not by Bread Alone, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Sunday Bulletins, 1990-2005 (Box 31)
  - Newsletter, The Visitor, 1990-2005 (Box 31)
  - Building use sheets, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Board of Worship and Christian Concern minutes, 1990-2005 (Box 31)
  - Board of Trustee minutes, 1990-2002 (Box 32)
  - Board of Christian Education minutes, 1990-2002 (Box 32)
  - Church cabinet minutes, 1990-2005 (Box 32)
  - Annual reports, 1990-2005 (Box 32)
  - Membership/friends directory, 1990-1999 (Box 32)
  - Early membership/friends data, ca. 1970s-1980s (Box 32)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1990-2002 (Box 32)
  - Annual Treasurer's reports, ca. 1990s (Box 32)
  - NYS ABC Women's Ministry magazine, n.d. (Box 32)
  - NYS ABC upstate home projects, n.d. (Box 32)
  - ABC First Baptist Women's Fellowship Notes, n.d. (Box 32)
  - ABC Valley Forge misc. information, n.d. (Box 32)
  - ABC correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 32)
  - Women's Interfaith Institute (outside organization), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Durham Trust (outside organization), n.d. (Box 32)
  - Ithaca area church and community day care, ca. 1990 (Box 32)
  - Meals-on-wheels, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Garage sales, 1995-2001 (Box 32)
  - Early Office Procedures, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Congregational meeting minutes, 1990-1999 (Box 32)
  - Music committee minutes and hymnal committe minutes (Box 33)
  - Centennial committee minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 33)
  - Every member canvass (pledge drive), 1990-2005 (Box 33)
  - Bosnian student project resettlement, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Resettlement of refugees, ca. 1980s (Box 33)
  - Resettlement of refugees, n.d. (Box 33)
    Duc Nguyen & Family; Koketso/Setshwaelo; Olebeng/Setshwaelo; Nhung Nguyen; Kyan Than & Family; Girich - Plotnikov Goncharenko; Desmangles, Ossee & Robert; Lingli (mother & daughter); Tarasevich Family
- Series II. Letters regarding construction of new church
  - Fundraising pamphlet by Robert T. Jones, Feb. 1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Feb. 4, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Feb. 7, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Robert to Mrs. A. B. Cornell, May 18, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Quarterly Review, May 22, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gaskell, E. B., Feb. 18, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Apr. 8, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hays, Mrs. J. B., Apr. 12, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Munro, David A., Apr. 23, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Caldwell, S. A., Apr. 24, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ambler, Mrs. J. V., Apr. 26, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Day, H. S., Apr. 26, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Constant, Mrs. Mary T., Apr. 28, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Armitage, Thomas, Apr. 29, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, F. W., May 1, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hurst, H. F. [Hunt?], May 1, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Grimwood, H. W., May 1, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hollis, F. C., May 2, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Houghton, Henry, May 5, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hiscox, C. E., May 5, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Utter, S. S., May 6, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Seymour, R. G., May 6, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Waffle, A. E., May 8, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - White, E. D., May 7, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Adams, J. E., Jr., May 7, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hays, Jacob, May 8, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Capeau, E. A., May 8, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ransom, Rastus S., May 8, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pyle, Wm. S., May 16, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Perry, James W., May 9, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Adams, J. Melvin, May 10, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Blood, Geo. A., May 10, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Peck, W. S., Bro. & Co., May 10, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wayland, Francis, May 10, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Woolverton, Geo. A., May 10, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Alfred, May 12, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Waters, Horace, May 14, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Grimwood, H. W., May 19, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hills, John, May 20, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Peabody, H. H., May 21, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Townsend, John P., May 22, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chase, H. G., May 26, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hohne, Wm., June 3, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Thurber, C. H., June 5, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Walker, M. Wallis, June 6, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Adams, R. J., June 16, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Batterson, Jas. G., June 20, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Andrews, E. Benj., June 21, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brokaw, Joseph, June 26, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cruly, J. G., June 28, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Overhiser, J. C., July 5, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pyle, Jas., July 12, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, John D., July 14, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Grippin, Wm. A., July 15, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Pyle, Jas., July 16, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Calvert, J. S., July 17, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mapelodin, M. J., July 23, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Atwater, E. W. (Jackson Sanitarium), July 31, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wheeler, Linn E., Aug. 1, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rogers, George D., Aug. 15, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Andrews, E. Benj., Aug. 18, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Sept. 2, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rogers, George D., Aug. 20, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Thomson, Lemon, Sept. 6, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Sleicher, Wm. Jr., Sept. 1, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - McCutchen, C. W., Sept. 18, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Oct. 21, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Culver, M. H., Oct. 22, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cotton, William H., Nov. 13, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 3)